Miklos Rozsa Papers
Miklos Rozsa Papers
- Compositions
  - By Rózsa, unnumbered
    - Tema con Variasioni, unbound reproduction (Oversize 99)
    - The Thief of Baghdad (Short suite), unbound handwritten composition (Oversize 100)
    - Three Pieces for Violin and Piano, unbound handwritten composition (Oversize 100)
    - The Time Machine, unbound handwritten composition (Oversize 101)
    - Tirolicume/Himkalkodjeir, unbound handwritten composition (Oversize 101)
    - Toccata, unbound handwritten composition (Oversize 101)
    - Trio fur Klavier, Violine und Viola, unbound handwritten composition (Oversize 132)
    - Trio für Klavier, Violine und Viola, unbound reproduction (Box 4)
    - Two Songs for Mezzo Soprano and Piano: "Un Jardin Dans La Nuit" and "Beasts of Burden", unbound handwritten composition (Oversize 133)
    - Two Songs for Mezzo Soprano and Piano: "Un Jardin Dans La Nuit" and "Beasts of Burden", spiral-bound reproduction (Oversize 334)
    - Two Stucke fur Violincello und Klavier, unbound reproduction (Oversize 134)
    - Unidentified (Foxtrot), unbound reproduction (Oversize 135)
    - Unidentified fragments, unbound reproduction (Oversize 136)
    - Varosliget Suite, unbound handwritten composition and reproductions (Oversize 137)
    - Vierle Schlageu, unbound handwritten composition (Oversize 137)
    - Zwei Ungarisch Tansstucke fur violine und Klavier, unbound reproduction (Oversize 138)
  - By Rózsa, numbered
    - Op. 01, Serenade fur Streich Trio, unbound handwritten composition (Oversize 18)
    - Op. 01, Trio (Serenade) für Violine, Viola und Violoncello, published sheet music (Box 1)
    - Op. 01, Trio (Serenade) für Violine, Viola und Violoncello, published sheet music (Box 1)
    - Op. 01, Trio (Serenade) für Violine, Viola und Violoncello, unbound composition in copyist's hand (Oversize 333)
    - Op. 01, Trio (Serenade) für Violine, Viola und Violoncello: Viola, published sheet music (Box 1)
    - Op. 01, Trio (Serenade) für Violine, Viola und Violoncello: Viola, published sheet music (Oversize 333)
    - Op. 01, Trio (Serenade) für Violine, Viola und Violoncello: Violin, published sheet music (Oversize 333)
    - Op. 01, Trio (Serenade) für Violine, Viola und Violoncello: Violin, published sheet music (Oversize 333)
    - Op. 01, Trio (Serenade) für Violine, Viola und Violoncello: Violoncello, published sheet music (Box 1)
    - Op. 01, Trio (Serenade) für Violine, Viola und Violoncello: Violoncello, published sheet music (Oversize 333)
    - Op. 01, Trio fur Violine, Viola un Violoncello, published sheet music and spiral-bound reproduction (Oversize 19)
    - Op. 02, Piano quintet, bound reproduction (Box 1)
    - Op. 02, Quintett in f moll, published sheet music (Oversize 20)
    - Op. 02, Quintett in f moll für Klavier, 2 Violinen, Viola und Violoncell, published sheet music (Box 1)
    - Op. 03, Rhapsodie for Violincello and Piano, published sheet music with handwritten inserts (Box 1)
    - Op. 03, Rhapsodie für Violoncello und Orchester, published sheet music (Box 1)
    - Op. 03, Rhapsodie für Violoncello und Orchester, published sheet music (Box 1)
    - Op. 04, Variationen uber ein ungarische Bauernleid, published sheet music (Oversize 21)
    - Op. 04, Variations on a Hungarian Peasant Song for violin and orchestra, bound reproduction (Oversize 334)
    - Op. 04, Variations on a Hungarian Peasant Song for violin and piano, unbound negatives (Box 1)
    - Op. 04, Variations on a Hungarian Peasant Song for violin and piano, bound reproduction (Box 1)
    - Op. 05, Nordungarische Bauernlieder und Tanze, published sheet music (Oversize 22)
    - Op. 05, Nordungarische Bauernlieder und Tänze (Kleine Suite) for violin and piano, published sheet music (Box 1)
    - Op. 05, North Hungarian Peasant Songs and Dances, spiral-bound reproduction (Oversize 23)
    - Op. 06, Quartet fur 2 Violines, Viola und Violoncello, unbound handwritten composition (Oversize 24)
    - Op. 07, Duo for violin and piano, published sheet music (Box 1)
    - Op. 07, Duo fur Violine und Klavier, published sheet music (Oversize 25)
    - Op. 08, Duo for violincello and piano, published sheet music (Box 1)
    - Op. 08, Duo for violincello and piano, published sheet music (Box 1)
    - Op. 08, Duo for violincello and piano: Violincello, published sheet music (Box 1)
    - Op. 08, Duo fur Violoncell und Klavier, published sheet music (Oversize 26)
    - Op. 09, Variations pour Piano, published sheet music (Oversize 334)
    - Op. 09, Variations pour Piano, published sheet music (Box 2)
    - Op. 10, Serenade, unbound handwritten composition (Box 2)
    - Op. 10, Serenade fur Kleines Orchester, published sheet music (Oversize 27)
    - Op. 12, Bagatellen, piano solo, unbound handwritten composition and published sheet music (Oversize 28)
    - Op. 12, Bagatellen (Kleine Stücke für Spiel und Tanz), piano solo, published sheet music (Box 2)
    - Op. 12, Bagatellen (Kleine Stücke für Spiel und Tanz), piano solo, published sheet music (Box 2)
    - Op. 13a, Thema, Variationen und Finale fur Grosses Orchester, published sheet music (Oversize 29)
    - Op. 14, Pastorale fur Grosses Orchester, published sheet music (Oversize 30)
    - Op. 14, Three Hungarian Sketches, unbound handwritten composition and spiral-bound reproduction (Oversize 31)
    - Op. 14, Three Hungarian Sketches, published sheet music (Oversize 32)
    - Op. 14, Three Hungarian Sketches (Capriccio, Pastorale e Danza), published sheet music (Box 2)
    - Op. 15, Sonata for Two Violins, published sheet music (Oversize 33)
    - Op. 15a, Sonate für zwei Violinen, published sheet music (Box 2)
    - Op. 15a, Sonate fur Zwei Vionlinen, published sheet music (Oversize 34)
    - Op. 16a, Invocation, published sheet music (Oversize 35)
    - Op. 16b, Beasts of Burden, published sheet music (Box 2)
    - Op. 16b, Beasts of Burden, published sheet music (Box 2)
    - Op. 16b, Beasts of Burden, voice and piano, published sheet music (Oversize 36)
    - Op. 17, Concerto for String Orchestra, published sheet music with Rózsa's markings (Box 2)
    - Op. 17, Concerto for String Orchestra, published sheet music (Oversize 37)
    - Op. 17, Concerto for Strings, spiral-bound reproduction (Oversize 334)
    - Op. 17, Concerto for Strings, unbound handwritten composition (Oversize 38)
    - Op. 17, Konsert fur Streichorchester, published sheet music (Oversize 39)
    - Op. 17, Konzert für Streichorchester, published sheet music in German (Box 2)
    - Op. 18a, Lullaby, unbound handwritten composition and reproductions (Oversize 40)
    - Op. 18a, Lullaby, SSAA a cappella, published sheet music (Box 2)
    - Op. 18b, A Madrigal of Spring, SSA a cappella, published sheet music (Box 2)
    - Op. 18b, A Madrigal of Spring, SSA a cappella, published sheet music (Oversize 167)
    - Op. 19, Kaleidoscope: Six Miniatures for Small Orchestra, spiral-bound reproduction (Oversize 41)
    - Op. 19, Kaleidoscope for Flute and Pianoforte, arranged by Christopher Palmer, unbound reproduction in portfolio book (Box 2)
    - Op. 19, Kaleidoscope for piano solo, published sheet music with Rózsa's markings (Box 2)
    - Op. 19, Kaleidoscope for piano solo, unbound reproduction (Box 2)
    - Op. 19, Kaleidoscope for piano solo, published sheet music (Oversize 42)
    - Op. 19 No. 1, Kaleidoscope for piano solo: March, published sheet music (Box 2)
    - Op. 19 No. 2, Kaleidoscope for piano solo: Zingara, published sheet music (Box 2)
    - Op. 19 No. 2, Kaleidoscope for piano solo: Zingara, published sheet music (Box 2)
    - Op. 19 No. 3, Kaleidoscope for piano solo: Musette, published sheet music (Box 2)
    - Op. 19 No. 4, Kaleidoscope for piano solo: Berceuse, published sheet music (Box 2)
    - Op. 19 No. 5, Kaleidoscope for piano solo: Chinese Carillon, published sheet music (Box 2)
    - Op. 19 No. 6, Kaleidoscope for piano solo: Burlesque, published sheet music (Box 2)
    - Op. 19 No. 6, Kaleidoscope for piano solo: Burlesque, published sheet music (Box 2)
    - Op. 20, Sonata for Piano, unbound handwritten composition (Oversize 43)
    - Op. 20, Sonate for piano solo, published sheet music (Box 2)
    - Op. 20, Sonate for piano solo, published sheet music (Box 2)
    - Op. 20, Sonate fur Klavier, published sheet music (Oversize 44)
    - Op. 21, Motette (For Everything There Is A Season), SATB a cappella, published sheet music in German and English (Box 2)
    - Op. 21, Motette (To Everything There Is A Season), SATB a cappella, published sheet music in German and English (Box 2)
    - Op. 21, To Everything There Is a Season, unbound handwritten composition and published sheet music (Oversize 45)
    - Op. 22, Second String Quartet, unbound negatives (Box 2)
    - Op. 22, Second String Quartet, unbound handwritten composition (Oversize 46)
    - Op. 22, Streichquartett, published sheet music (Box 2)
    - Op. 22, Streichquartett, published sheet music (Oversize 47)
    - Op. 22, String Quartet, spiral-bound miniature reproduction (Box 2)
    - Op. 22, String Quartet, published sheet music (Box 2)
    - Op. 22, String Quartet, spiral-bound reproduction (Box 2)
    - Op. 22, String Quartet, published sheet music (Oversize 48)
    - Op. 23, The Vintner's Daughter: Twelve Variations on a French Folk Song for piano, published sheet music with Rózsa's markings (Box 3)
    - Op. 23, The Vintner's Daughter: Twelve Variations on a French Folk Song for piano, published sheet music (Box 3)
    - Op. 23, Variations on a French Folksong "La Fille du Vigneron", unbound handwritten composition (Oversize 49)
    - Op. 23a, The Vintner's Daughter: Twelve Variations on a French Folk Song, published sheet music (Box 3)
    - Op. 24, Concerto for Violin and Orchestra, published sheet music with Rózsa's markings (Oversize 50)
    - Op. 24, Concerto for Violin and Orchestra, bound reproduction and published sheet music (Oversize 51)
    - Op. 24, Concerto for Violin and Orchestra, bound handwritten composition (Oversize 52)
    - Op. 24, Concerto for Violin and Orchestra, published sheet music (Oversize 53)
    - Op. 24, Concerto for Violin and Orchestra, spiral-bound reproduction (Oversize 54)
    - Op. 24, Violin-Konzert, published sheet music (Box 3)
    - Op. 25, Ungarische Serenade, published sheet music and bound reproduction with Rózsa's markings (Oversize 55)
    - Op. 26, Concert Overture, full orchestra, published sheet music (Oversize 56)
    - Op. 26a, Overture to a Symphony Concert, published sheet music and onionskin masters (Oversize 57)
    - Op. 26a, Overture to a Symphony Concert, spiral-bound reproduction (Oversize 58)
    - Op. 27, Sonatina for Clarinet Solo, published sheet music (Box 3)
    - Op. 27, Sonatina for Clarinet Solo, published sheet music and onionskin masters (Oversize 59)
    - Op. 28, Notturno Ungherese fur Grosses Orchester, unbound handwritten composition and reproductions (Oversize 60)
    - Op. 29, Concerto for Violin, Cello and Orchestra, unbound handwritten composition and spiral-bound reproduction (Oversize 61)
    - Op. 29, Concerto for Violin, Cello and Orchestra, unbound handwritten composition (Oversize 62)
    - Op. 29, Sinfonia concertante für Violine, Violoncello und Orchester, published sheet music (Box 3)
    - Op. 29, Sinfonia Concertante fur Violine, Violoncello, und Orchester, published sheet music (Oversize 63)
    - Op. 29a, Tema Con Variazioni fur Violine, Violoncello und Kammerorchester, published sheet music and unbound reproduction with Rózsa's markings (Oversize 64)
    - Op. 30, Die Eitelkeiten des Lebens (The Vanities of Life) Motette, mixed choir a cappella, published sheet music (Oversize 65)
    - Op. 30, Die Eitelkeiten des Lebens (The Vanities of Life) Motette, mixed choir a cappella, published sheet music in German and English (Box 3)
    - Op. 30, Die Eitelkeiten des Lebens (The Vanities of Life) Motette, mixed choir a cappella, unbound handwritten composition (Box 3)
    - Op. 31, Concerto per Pianoforte e Orchestra, unbound handwritten composition (Oversize 66)
    - Op. 31, Concerto per Pianoforte e Orchestra, spiral-bound reproduction (Oversize 67)
    - Op. 31, Concerto per Pianoforte e Orchestra, bound reproduction with Rózsa's markings (Oversize 68)
    - Op. 31, Concerto per Pianoforte e Orchestra, bound reproduction with Rózsa's markings (Oversize 69)
    - Op. 31, Concerto per Pianoforte e Orchestra, bound reproduction (Oversize 70)
    - Op. 31, Konsert fur Klavier und Orchester, published sheet music (Oversize 71)
    - Op. 31, Konzert für Klavier und Orchester, published sheet music (Box 3)
    - Op. 31, Konzert für Klavier und Orchester, published sheet music with Rózsa's markings (Box 3)
    - Op. 32, Concerto for Cello and Orchestra, unbound handwritten composition (Oversize 72)
    - Op. 32, Konsert fur Violoncello und Orchester, unbound handwritten composition (Oversize 73)
    - Op. 32, Konsert fur Violoncello und Orchester, spiral-bound handwritten composition (Oversize 73A)
    - Op. 32, Konsert fur Violoncello und Orchester, spiral-bound reproduction (Oversize 74)
    - Op. 32, Konsert fur Violoncello und Orchester, published sheet music (Oversize 75)
    - Op. 32, Konzert für Violoncello und Orchester, published sheet music (Box 3)
    - Op. 32, Konzert für Violoncello und Orchester, published sheet music (Box 3)
    - Op. 33, Three Pieces for Orchester, bound handwritten composition (Oversize 76)
    - Op. 33, Tripartita fur Orchester, published sheet music (Oversize 77)
    - Op. 33, Tripartita fur Orchester, unbound handwritten composition (Oversize 78)
    - Op. 33, Tripartita für Orchester, published sheet music in German (Box 3)
    - Op. 34, The Twenty-Third Psalm, SATB, published sheet music and unbound handwritten composition (Oversize 79)
    - Op. 34, The Twenty-Third Psalm (The Lord is my shepherd), SATB a cappella, published sheet music (Box 3)
    - Op. 34, The Twenty-Third Psalm (The Lord is my shepherd), SATB a cappella, published sheet music (Box 3)
    - Op. 35, Three Chinese Songs for Mixed Choir, unbound handwritten composition (Oversize 80)
    - Op. 35b No. 2, Three Chinese Poems: Swallow, Swallow, SATB a cappella, published sheet music (Box 3)
    - Op. 35c, Three Chinese Poems: The Cuckoo, published sheet music (Box 3)
    - Op. 36, Toccata Capricciosa, unbound handwritten composition (Oversize 81)
    - Op. 36, Toccata capricciosa for cello, unbound reproduction (Box 3)
    - Op. 36, Toccata capricciosa for cello, unbound reproduction (Box 3)
    - Op. 36, Toccata capricciosa for cello, unbound reproduction with Rózsa's markings (Box 3)
    - Op. 36, Toccata capricciosa for cello, unbound reproduction with Rózsa's markings (Box 3)
    - Op. 36, Toccata capricciosa für Violoncello-solo, published sheet music (Box 3)
    - Op. 37, Concerto for Violin and Orchestra, unbound reproduction (Box 4)
    - Op. 37, Concerto for Violin and Orchestra, unbound handwritten composition (Oversize 334)
    - Op. 37, Concerto per Viola e Orchestra, unbound handwritten composition and reproductions (Oversize 82)
    - Op. 37, Concerto per Viola e Orchestra, spiral-bound reproduction with markings (Oversize 83)
    - Op. 37, Concerto per Viola e Orchestra, spiral-bound reproduction (Oversize 84)
    - Op. 37, Concerto per Viola e Orchestra: viola and piano, published sheet music (Oversize 85)
    - Op. 37, Konzert fur Viola und Orchester, spiral-bound reproduction (Oversize 86)
    - Op. 37, Konzert für Viola und Orchester, published sheet music (Box 4)
    - Op. 38, Streichquartett Nr. 2, published sheet music (Box 4)
    - Op. 39, Sonata per Flauto Solo, published sheet music (Box 4)
    - Op. 39, Sonata per Flauto Solo, published sheet music with Rózsa's corrections (Box 4)
    - Op. 39, Sonata per Flauto Solo, published sheet music with Rózsa's corrections (Box 4)
    - Op. 39, Sonata per Flauto Solo, published music, bound (Box 4)
    - Op. 39, Sonata per Flauto Solo, unbound reproduction (Box 4)
    - Op. 39, Sonata per Flauto Solo, unbound handwritten score in Rozsa's hand; one original, one reproduction; 2 copies (Box 4)
    - Op. 39, Sonata per Flauto Solo, unbound score in copyist's hand (Box 4)
    - Op. 39, Sonata per Flauto Solo, unbound reproduction in copyist's hand with Rózsa's markings (Box 4)
    - Op. 39, Sonata per Flauto Solo, unbound reproduction with Rózsa's markings (Box 4)
    - Op. 40, Sonata per Violino Solo, unbound handwritten composition (Oversize 87)
    - Op. 40, Sonata per Violino Solo, unbound masters for publication (Box 4)
    - Op. 40, Sonata per Violino Solo, spiral-bound reproduction (Box 4)
    - Op. 40, Sonata per Violino Solo, spiral-bound reproduction of 2nd proofs with Rózsa's markings (Box 4)
    - Op. 40, Sonata per Violino Solo, unbound reproduction (Box 4)
    - Op. 40, Sonata per Violino Solo, unbound reproduction (Box 4)
    - Op. 40, Sonata per Violino Solo, spiral-bound reproduction (Box 4)
    - Op. 40, Sonate für Violine, published sheet music (Box 4)
    - Op. 41, Sonata per Clarinetto Solo, published sheet music (Box 4)
    - Op. 41, Sonata per Clarinetto Solo, unbound reproduction with Rózsa's markings (Box 4)
    - Op. 41, Sonata per Clarinetto Solo, unbound reproduction with Rózsa's markings (Oversize 334)
    - Op. 41, Sonata per Clarinetto Solo, unbound handwritten composition (Oversize 88)
    - Op. 42, Sonata for Guitar, published sheet music (Box 4)
    - Op. 42, Sonata for Guitar, bound reproduction (Box 4)
    - Op. 43, Sonata for Oboe Solo, published sheet music (Box 4)
    - Op. 44, Introduction and Allegro for Viola Solo, published sheet music (Box 4)
    - Op. 45, Sonatina for Ondes Martenot, handwritten composition (Box 4)
    - Op. 45, Sonatina for Ondes Martenot, published sheet music (Box 4)
  - By Nic Tomay (Rozsa pseudonym)
    - "A Tout Petits Pas", published sheet music (Oversize 103)
    - "Bobby Cheri", published sheet music (Oversize 104)
    - "A La Conquete de Bonheur", published sheet music (Oversize 102)
    - "Dans Le Soir Profond", published sheet music (Oversize 105)
    - "Dans Mon Pou Volant", published sheet music (Oversize 106)
    - "Diplomate", published sheet music (Oversize 107)
    - "Doguediguedou!", published sheet music (Oversize 108)
    - "Entrons Dans La Danse", published sheet music (Oversize 109)
    - "Fantaisie Tzigane", published sheet music (Oversize 110)
    - "J'ai Gardé Mon Coeur", published sheet music (Oversize 111)
    - "Je Ne Peux Y Penser Sans Sourire", published sheet music (Oversize 112)
    - "Je Ne Veux Plus D'amour", published sheet music (Oversize 113)
    - "Je N'Sais Vraiment Pas Porquoi", published sheet music (Oversize 114)
    - "Je T'Ai Regarde", published sheet music (Oversize 115)
    - "Un Jour De Beau Temps", published sheet music (Oversize 128)
    - "Leaves Turn Yellow", published sheet music (Oversize 118)
    - "Ne Me Parle Jamais D'Amour", published sheet music (Oversize 119)
    - "Ne M'En Parle Plus", published sheet music (Oversize 120)
    - "Non, Ce N'Est Pas Moi", published sheet music (Oversize 121)
    - "Performance", published sheet music (Oversize 122)
    - "La Petit Femm' Que L'On Aime", published sheet music (Oversize 116)
    - "Un Petit Nid", published sheet music (Oversize 129)
    - "Plus De Mesure...", published sheet music (Oversize 123)
    - "Quand On a Turbiné Toute La Semaine", published sheet music (Oversize 124)
    - "Rataplan", published sheet music (Oversize 125)
    - "Reminiscences of the Puszta", published sheet music and unbound handwritten composition (Oversize 126)
    - "Le Secret Du Vrai Bonheur", published sheet music (Oversize 117)
    - "Two For Me", published sheet music (Oversize 127)
    - "Vivons Ce Doux Poeme", published sheet music (Oversize 130)
    - "Whist", published sheet music (Oversize 131)
  - By others
    This subseries contains musical compositions by Rózsa's colleagues and friends.
    - Alwyn, William, "Derby Day": Overture for Full Orchestra, miniature score (Box 5)
    - Alwyn, William, "Lyra Angelica": Concerto for Harp and String Orchestra, miniature score (Box 5)
    - Andersen, Michael, "Six Mezzo Soprano Songs", published sheet music (Box 5)
    - Balazs, Frederic, "Passacaglia (Variations on a Theme of Greeting)", spiral-bound reproduction (Oversize 139)
    - Banchieri, Adriano, "Barca di Venetia per Padova" for five voices, published sheet music (Box 5)
    - Brahms, Johannes, "Hungarian Dance No. 4" for piano, published sheet music with Rózsa's markings (Box 5)
    - Cadman, Charles Wakefield, "A Mad Empress Remembers": Tone Drama for Violincello and Piano, published sheet music (Box 5)
    - Castelnuovo-Tedesco, Mario, "2 Songs from the Jungle Book", unbound reproduction (Box 5)
    - Castelnuovo-Tedesco, Mario, "A Dante Sonnet (Un Sonetto di Dante)", published sheet music (Box 5)
    - Castelnuovo-Tedesco, Mario, "Endymion", SAATTBB a cappella, published sheet music (Box 5)
    - Castelnuovo-Tedesco, Mario, "Evangelion", bound reproduction (Box 5)
    - Castelnuovo-Tedesco, Mario, "On the Grasshopper and Cricket", S.S.S.A., published sheet music (Box 5)
    - Castelnuovo-Tedesco, Mario, "Preludio e Fanfara (Two Études in the Twelve-Tone System)" For Piano, unbound reproduction (Box 5)
    - Castelnuovo-Tedesco, Mario, "Psyche", S.A.T.B., published sheet music (Box 5)
    - Castelnuovo-Tedesco, Mario, "The Nightingale (Le Rossignol)", published sheet music (Box 5)
    - Castelnuovo-Tedesco, Mario, "Venice", T.T.B.B. a cappella, published sheet music (Box 5)
    - Castelnuovo-Tedesco, Mario, Op. 152, "Romancero Gitano" for mixed choir and guitar, published sheet music (Box 5)
    - Castelnuovo-Tedesco, Mario, Op. 155, "2nd Piano Quintet (Ricordi della Campagna Toscana) (Memories of the Tuscan Countryside)", unbound reproduction (Oversize 140)
    - Castelnuovo-Tedesco, Mario, Op. 170 No. 17, "Ricercare (sul nome di Luigi Dallapiccola)", published sheet music (Box 5)
    - Castelnuovo-Tedesco, Mario, Op. 170 No. 25, "Hungarian Serenade (on the name of Miklós Rózsa)" for violin and piano, unbound original composition (Box 5)
    - Castelnuovo-Tedesco, Mario, Op. 173, "Three Shelley Songs": "One Word is too Often Profaned", S.S.A., published sheet music (Box 5)
    - Castelnuovo-Tedesco, Mario, Op. 173, "Three Shelley Songs": "The Fountains Mingle With the River", S.S.A., published sheet music (Box 5)
    - Castelnuovo-Tedesco, Mario, Op. 173, "Three Shelley Songs": "When The Lamp Is Shatter'd", S.S.A., published sheet music (Box 5)
    - Castelnuovo-Tedesco, Mario, Op. 174 No. 1, "The Word", S.A.T.B. a cappella, published sheet music (Box 5)
    - Castelnuovo-Tedesco, Mario, Op. 174 No. 2, "The Light", S.A.T.B. a cappella, published sheet music (Box 5)
    - Castelnuovo-Tedesco, Mario, Op. 183, "The Fiery Furnace", Piano and Vocal Score, published sheet music (Box 5)
    - Castelnuovo-Tedesco, Mario, Op. 203, "3rd String Quartet (Casa al Dono)", spiral-bound reproduction (Oversize 141)
    - Coates, Albert, "Pickwick: An Opera in three Acts", vocal score, published libretto (Box 5)
    - Cortese, Luigi, Op. 44, "Fantasia" for orchestra, published sheet music (Box 5)
    - Gallagher, Jack, "Concert Overture", spiral-bound reproduction (Box 6)
    - Gallagher, Jack, "Elegy", S.A.T.B. a cappella, published sheet music (Box 6)
    - Gallagher, Jack, "Sonata for Piano", published sheet music (Box 6)
    - Gallagher, Jack, "Sonata" for unaccompanied trumpet, published sheet music (Box 6)
    - Gallagher, Jack, "Toccata for Brass Quintet", published sheet music (Box 6)
    - Gershwin, George, "Porgy and Bess": "My Man's Gone Now", published sheet music (Box 6)
    - Grabner, Hermann, "Orgel-Choralbuch", bound reproduction (Oversize 7)
    - Grabner, Hermann, Op. 1, "Konsert in alten Stil für drei Violinen", published sheet music (Box 6)
    - Grabner, Hermann, Op. 31, "Gesang zur Sonne", published sheet music (Box 6)